Guide to the Vassar College Biographical Files, 1872-2023
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- H
  - Hadley, Katherine (Blodgett)
  - Hadley, Mary (Hill) – SEE Randolph, Mary (Hill)
  - Hadley, Morris
  - Haeflinger, C. Fred, Jr.
  - Haffar, Amhad R.
  - Hager, Casey
  - Hager, Peter A. (trustee)
  - Hagstrom, Ann H.
  - Hague, William (trustee)
  - Haight, Elizabeth Hazelton, [5 folders]
  - Halberstadt, Amy G.
  - Hale, Sarah Josepha, [6 folders]
  - Halecki, Oscar
  - Hales, John
  - Halfen, Lawrence N.
  - Hall, Dr. Lucy
  - Hall, William Sterling
  - Hallett, Judith Peller
  - Halpern-Amaru, Betsy
  - Hamilton, Carlos D.
  - Hamilton, Gwendolyn – SEE Stevens, Gwendolyn Hamilton
  - Hammond, Christina
  - Hammond, Richard T.
  - Hanna, Judith B
  - Harloe, William
  - Harmon, Oskar
  - Harper, James
  - Harper, William Rainey
  - Harriford, Diane
  - Harrington, Christine B.
  - Harringon, Natalie
  - Harris, Barbara S.
  - Harris, Benjamin F.
  - Harris, Brian
  - Harris, Ira
  - Harris, Judith M.
  - Harris, Luke
  - Harrison, Nancy (Blaine) (trustee)
  - Harry, Jean L., [2 folders]
  - Hartnack, Justus
  - Hartshorn, Sue
  - Hartt, Charles Frederick
  - Harvey, David D.
  - Haskell, Charlotte C.
  - Haskell, Henry S.
  - Haskell, Lucy A.
  - Hass, Stephen
  - Hauck, Arthur
  - Hauptman, William T.
  - Havelock, Christine M.
  - Havemeyer, Eugenie (Aiguier) (trustee)
  - Haviland, Beverly
  - Hawkins, Dorothy Lawson
  - Hawkins, Harriett B.
  - Healea, Monica, [2 folders]
  - Healy, Anne
  - Heath, Frederick M.
  - Heath, William R.
  - Hedges, Douglas W.
  - Heinemann, Eric G.
  - Heinlein, Mary Virginia, [3 folders]
  - Heinrich, Lynne L.
  - Heins, William
  - Heller, Celia Stopnicka
  - Hellerstein, Nina S.
  - Helpern, Alice J.
  - Helt, Jacob
  - Hemmes, Richard B.
  - Hendershot, Heather
  - Hendler, Marjorie
  - Hennessey, William J.
  - Hennessy, Leslie Griffin
  - Henriquez-Urena, Camila
  - Henry, Charles
  - Henry, George
  - Herbst, Lawrence A.
  - Herr, Linda L.
  - Herring, Frances White
  - Herron, Geraldine
  - Hersey, Heloise Edwins
  - Herzfeld, Michael
  - Heston, Lilla
  - Hevenor, Robert H.
  - Heyse, John V.
  - Higgins, Dorothy
  - Higgins, June B.
  - Hill, Anthony D.
  - Hill, Catherine, [2 folders]
  - Hiil, Hope M.
  - Hill, Ida (Thallon)
  - Hill, Vassie (James)
  - Hill, William T.
  - Hillis, Mary
  - Hills, Thomas McDougall
  - Hincks, John M (trustee)
  - Hinkel, Charles J.
  - Hinkel, Minna
  - Hirschhorn, Joan (Morgenthau) (trustee)
  - Hitchcock, Henry Russell
  - Hite, Katie
  - Hoadley, Margaret A.
  - Ho, Ben
  - Ho, Jody Thomas
  - Hoagwood, Terence
  - Hodas, Daniel H.
  - Hodges, Norman Edward
  - Hoernes, Gerhard E.
  - Hoffberg, Mark B.
  - Hoffberg, Susan (Mrs. Mark)
  - Hofrichter, Ruth J.
  - Hogya, Giles
  - Höhn, Maria
  - Hole, Winston L.
  - Holland, Leicester B.
  - Holmes, Genevieve L.
  - Holmes, John Grier
  - Holmstrom, Lasse
  - Holton, Pari
  - Honke, Sylvia
  - Hopkins, J. Roy
  - Hopper, Grace Murray, [2 folders]
  - Hopper, Steven Phillip
  - Horowitz, Tamara
  - Horwitz, Barry
  - Horst, Jeff
  - Houghton, Norris, [3 folders]
  - Houseman, John
  - Hover, Violet Slinsen
  - Hovland, David
  - Howe, Harold II (trustee)
  - Howe, Nancy
  - Howlett, Christine
  - Howson, Alice Guest
  - Howson, John Howard, [2 folders]
  - Hoynes, William
  - Hsu, Hua
  - Hubbard, Marguerite B.
  - Hubbard, Mary Ellen
  - Huder, Carmen
  - Hudson, Susan
  - Huenik, Peter G.
  - Hummel, Holly K.
  - Humphrey, John W.
  - Humpstone, Mabel (Hastings) (trustee)
  - Hunkins, Sterling
  - Hunter, Mary Alice
  - Hunter, Virginia J.
  - Huntington, F. D. (trustee)
  - Hutchins, Robert J.
  - Hutchinson, James L., Jr.
  - Hutchinson, Ruth Gillette
  - Hyde, Mary (Crapo)
  - Hytier, Adrienne Doris
- I
  - I-
  - Ide, Nancy M.
  - Idelson, Shirley
  - Idoine, Lucienne
  - Ignatow, David
  - Imbrie, Ann E.
  - Infield, Henrik (Heinrich) Freier and Mita
  - Ingerman, Brett
  - Innis, George (trustee)
  - Irvine, David F.
  - Irwin, Vera
  - Iswolsky, Helene
- J
  - Ja-Je
  - Joc-Johnson
  - Johnst-Joy
  - Ju-Jz
  - Jackson, Jane-Lee
  - Jackson, Judy
  - Jackson, Lauren W.
  - Jackson, Mary Ann
  - Jacob, Charles E.
  - Jacobs, Judith
  - Jaeger, Dr. Rita
  - Jaenson, Marjorie Carol
  - Jakuc, Monica M.
  - Janney, Mary Draper (trustee)
  - Janoff, Mitchell
  - Jansson, David
  - Jarrow, E. H. Rick
  - Jarvis, Kim
  - Jasulic, Marc
  - Jeanneney, Mary Louise
  - Jefferson, John H.
  - Jefferson, Joseph
  - Jehle, Geoffrey A.
  - Jemiolo, David K.
  - Jenkins, Peter E.
  - Jennings, Andrew M.
  - Jeudevine, Marion E.
  - Jewett, Milo P., [5 folders]
  - John, Kathryn Ann
  - Johnsen, John H., [2 folders]
  - Johnson, Burges, [3 folders]
  - Johnson, C. Colton
  - Johnson, Corinne L.
  - Johnson, Elizabeth Forrest (trustee)
  - Johnson, Glen
  - Johnson, Herbert C. Jr.
  - Johnson, J. William M.D.
  - Johnson, Jane T.
  - Johnson, Jeh Vincent, [2 folders]
  - Johnson, Kenneth A.
  - Johnson, Lee
  - Johnson, Lucille
  - Johnson, M. Glen, [2 folders]
  - Johnson, Mildred
  - Johnson, Norma E.
  - Johnson, Patricia R., [2 folders]
  - Johnson, Paul
  - Johnson, Sharon L.
  - Johnson, Wade R.
  - Johnston, Lowell Douglas
  - Jolivette, Murray G.
  - Jones, Barbara
  - Jones, Ella Honera
  - Jones, Gilbert E. (trustee)
  - Jones, Jonathan D.
  - Jones, Wendell
  - Jordan, Mary Augusta
  - Joshi, Ram J.
  - Joyce, Michael
  - Juliano, Annette
  - Junco, Victoria (Mrs. Paul D. Meyer)
- K
  - Ka
  - Ke
  - Ki
  - Kl-Ko
  - Kr-Kz
  - Kaddar, Maureen
  - Kahn, Harris
  - Kahn, Jonathan
  - Kahn, Ludwig W.
  - Kalin, Jesse
  - Kambouropoulou, Polyxenie
  - Kamm, Charles
  - Kane, Eleanor C.
  - Kane, Jill B.
  - Kane, Paul
  - Kaplan Martha
  - Kapp, Caecille
  - Kapschutschenko, Ludmila
  - Karl, Patricia A.
  - Kassier, Theodore L.
  - Katan, Roger
  - Kataoka, Tetsuya
  - Kater, John L., Jr.
  - Katz, Joseph
  - Katz, Leon
  - Katz, Marjorie Fink
  - Katz, Minerva Ann
  - Katzenellenbogen, Adolph
  - Katzenellenbogen, Elisabeth
  - Katzowitz, Colleen
  - Kaufman, Jerome
  - Kaurouma, Patricia, [missing as of November 2004]
  - Kautz, James C.
  - Kava, Ruth
  - Kavanagh, Kathleen
  - Kearney, Eileen
  - Keeler, Mary Frear
  - Keith, Donna
  - Keller, Lisa
  - Keller, Suzanne
  - Kelley, David
  - Kelly, Sally
  - Kelly, William (trustee)
  - Kempton, Daniel R.
  - Kempton, Rudolf T.
  - Kendall, Martha B.
  - Kendrick, Georgia Avery (Mrs. J. Ryland)
  - Kendrick, J. Ryland, Rev.
  - Kenig, Lea
  - Kennedy, Ruby Jo Reeves
  - Kennett, David
  - Kennett, Susan Correll
  - Kent, Edward Allen
  - Kenworthy, Patricia
  - Kenyon, Helen, [3 folders]
  - Kerr, Cynthia
  - Kerr, Gordon L.
  - Kessler, Nevin
  - Ketchum, Elizabeth
  - Khamsyvoravong, Khambay
  - Kim, Sonja de Groot
  - Kimball, Grace
  - King, Elizabeth N.
  - King, Evalena
  - King, Maureen
  - King, William L.
  - Kingston, Robert
  - Kinnaird, John William
  - Kinnaird, Joan Kennedy
  - Kirkland, William H.
  - Kischkin, Georg
  - Kitchel, Anna
  - Kitcher, Philip S.
  - Kitzinger, Rachel
  - Kiviat, Esther
  - Klejment, Anne M.
  - Klein, Alice Cambell
  - Klimoff, Alexis
  - Klimoff, Louise
  - Klose, Donald Atwood
  - Kluge, Robert H.
  - Knapp, Janet
  - Knapp, William I.
  - Koch, Stuart G.
  - Koechlin, Tim
  - Koempel, Leslie H.
  - Koford, Kenneth
  - Kohl, Benjamin G.
  - Kopstein, Betsy
  - Kosmacher, Jeffrey B.
  - Korostoff, Jeffrey
  - Korte, Charles D.
  - Koutzen, Boris, [2 folders]
  - Kozloff, Sarah
  - Kraft, Michael
  - Kraut, Benny
  - Krautheimer, Richard, [2 folders]
  - Krenek, Ernst
  - Kristjansen, Harold B., [2 folders]
  - Kroll, Judith
  - Kroner, Richard
  - Kronsky, Betty
  - Krossner, William
  - Kuehn, Elaine K.
  - Kuemmerle, Clyde
  - Kuhn, Marianna Messinger
  - Kuhn-Osius, K. Eckhard
  - Kumar, Amitava
  - Kuntz, Eloise
  - Kurten, John L.
  - Kurtz, Paul W.
  - Kury, Gloria
  - Kutlow, Wendy
  - Kwiatoski, Deborah R.
- L
  - L-Lan
  - Lar-Laz
  - Lea-Lel
  - Lem-Lez
  - Li
  - Lo
  - Lu-Lz
  - Lacher, Maury
  - Lacher, Miriam Browner
  - Lachterman, David
  - Lacks, Bernice Kirk
  - Lacks, Mary Kirk
  - LaCugna, Catherine M.
  - Ladd, Nancy E.
  - Ladewig, James
  - Lake, David H.
  - Lalli, Richard
  - Lamb, Dorothy Davis
  - Lambert, Ronald T.
  - Lamble, Margaret
  - Lammers, Alfons
  - Lammert, Olive M.
  - La Mont, Barbara Gibson, [2 folders]
  - Lamson, Geneieve
  - Lanapoppi, Aleramo P.
  - Lancaster, Clay
  - Lane, Esther Porter Power
  - Lang, Mabel L.
  - Lang, William W.
  - Langdon, George D.
  - Lange, Garrett W.
  - Lange, Norman Jay
  - Langner, Helen P.
  - Langmuir, Mary Shattuck Fisher, [7 folders]
  - Lanier, Lyle H.
  - Larson, Ruth M.
  - Lasarte, Pedro C.
  - Lasry, Anita B.
  - Laszewski, Ronald T.
  - Lathrop, Edward
  - Lathrop, Julia C.
  - Lavery, Emmet
  - Lavin Camacho, Enrique
  - Lawton, Rebecca
  - Leach, Abby
  - Leach, Eleanor
  - LeClezio, Marguerite
  - Lee, Barbara
  - Lee, Dorothy D., [3 folders]
  - Lee, Jane
  - Lee, Jennete Perry
  - Lee, Karin
  - Lee, Maurice A.
  - Lee, Otis H.
  - Leffingwell, Russell Cornell (trustee)
  - Leggett, Paul
  - Lehman, Shirley Golove
  - Lehmann, Shirley Jeanne
  - Leitenberg, Milton
  - Leites, Edmund
  - Leittes, Judith (Axenzow)
  - Lelavandier, Marie H.
  - Leonard, Clair T.
  - Leonard, Eileen
  - Leonard, Katherine
  - Leonard, Peter, [2 folders]
  - Leppmann, Wolfgang
  - Lerner, Anita Marburg
  - Lessor, Edith S.
  - Levens, Dorothy, [2 folders]
  - Levertov, Denise
  - Levine, Morton
  - Levy, Charles K.
  - Lewis, Carolyn K.
  - Lewisohn, Margaret (trustee)
  - Lewittes, Judith A.
  - Lewkowicz, David J.
  - Leyvraz, Jean-Pierre
  - Liang, Hsi-Huey
  - Lichtenberg, Pat
  - Lieb, Gretchen
  - Linburn, Geoffrey E. M.D.
  - Lincoln, C. Eric
  - Lindberg, Beatrice M.
  - Lindbloom, Nancy Willard
  - Lindsay, Catherine
  - Lindsley, Margarete W.
  - Linner, Edward R., [2 folders]
  - Linter, Harold S.
  - Lipschutz, Elaine
  - Lipschutz, Ilse Hempel, [2 folders]
  - Lipton, Ellen Robin
  - Lipton, Lynn
  - LiSanti, Barbara
  - Littlehales, Lillian
  - Liu, Chen-Tung
  - Lochner, George
  - Lockwood, Annea F
  - Lockwood, Helen Drusilla, [4 folders]
  - Lloyd, Marion (Musser) (trustee)
  - Loeb, Frances L.
  - Loebl, Eugen
  - Löfgren, Ulla
  - Loose, Gerhard
  - Lord, Agnes and Frances
  - Lossing, Benson, [3 folders]
  - Lotarski, Suzanne S.
  - Lotz, Peter
  - Lotz, Wolfgang
  - Louie, David Wong
  - Lovell, Florence Bell
  - Lowe, Jeanne R.
  - Lowenthal, David
  - Lown, Clarence
  - Lowrey, Perrin H.
  - Lowry, Richard J.
  - Lubart, Henriette d’Arlin
  - Lucic, Karen
  - Lukach, Joan Mickelson
  - Lukas, Karen J.
  - Lumb, Ethel Sue, [2 folders]
  - Lumumba-Kasongo, Tukumbi
  - Lunt, William
  - Luper, Alan
  - Luther, Sally
  - Lutz, Alma, [3 folders]
  - Lyman, Christine (Ramsey)
  - Lyman, Hannah W., [2 folders]
  - Lyman, Mary Ely
  - Lynch, Hollis R.
  - Lyu, Claire
- M
  - M-MacI
  - Mack-MacW
  - Mad-Man
  - Man-Mar
  - Mat-Maz
  - Mea-Mell
  - Melz-Mey
  - Mic-Mil
  - Min-Mitch
  - Moe-More
  - Morg-Moye
  - Mue-Myh
  - Mar
  - Mat-Maz
  - Ma, May Chih-Mei
  - MacCabee, Mark
  - MacColl, Mary
  - MacCracken, Dr. Henry Noble, [75 folders]
  - MacCracken, Marjorie Dodd, [2 folders]
  - MacCracken family
  - MacDermott, Kathleen
  - Mace, Dean T.
  - Mace, Mary Ann
  - MacKechnie, Nancy S.
  - Mackenzie, Marla Orr
  - Mackie, Mary F.
  - MacLeish, Martha Hillard
  - MacLeod, Annie L.
  - Macmahon, Edna C., [2 folders]
  - Macurdy, Grace Harriet, [3 folders]
  - Madariaga, Pilarde
  - Madgwick, F. Roy
  - Maggio, Carol A.
  - Magidson, Beverly Weintraub
  - Magill, Roswell
  - Magoon, E.L. (trustee)
  - Magrath, William T.
  - Mahoney, Mary Eleanor
  - Mailler, Marion (Mackenzie) (trustee)
  - Main, James E.
  - Makemson, Maud, [2 folders]
  - Malbon, Elizabeth Struthers
  - Malley, Lynn
  - Mallon, Thomas, [2 folders]
  - Maltzoff, Nicholas
  - Mamiya, Lawrence
  - Manca, Pasqualina
  - Mandel, Patricia C. D.
  - Manheimer, Joan
  - Mann, Brian R.
  - Mann, Kate
  - Manuele, Elizabeth P.
  - Marburg, Clara
  - Marchi, Peggy
  - Markley, Robert
  - Marquez, Antonio
  - Marr, J. William
  - Marling, Karal Ann
  - Marsala, Donald
  - Marshall, Helaine W.
  - Marshall, Howard
  - Marshall, Natalie Junemann
  - Marthers, Paul
  - Martin, Elizabeth
  - Marvin, Jameson Neil
  - Mason, Gerald
  - Mason, Mary Gertrude
  - Massoff, Alan
  - Mastrangelo, Agnes J.
  - Mates, Thomas A.
  - Mauck, Mrs. Federico F. (trustee)
  - Maul, Shirley Anna
  - Maxwell, Alan I.
  - Mayer, Janet
  - Mayne, Jeffrey
  - Mayo, Margarita de
  - Mayorga, Susanna
  - Mbatha, Mphiwa B.
  - McAfee, Mildred (Mrs. Horton), [3 folders]
  - McAndrew, John
  - McArthur, Robert E.
  - McCaleb, Ella
  - McCaleb, Florence
  - McCall, David B. (trustee)
  - McCann, William
  - McCarthy, Barbara C.
  - McCarthy, Elizabeth
  - McCarthy, John B.
  - McCarthy, Louise (Robley) (trustee)
  - McCarthy, Michael H.
  - McCaughey, Elizabeth P.
  - McCauley, Dee
  - McClanahan, Richard
  - McCloskey, Mark A.
  - McCloskey, Susan
  - McComb, Peter, [2 folders]
  - McConaughy, James L. (trustee)
  - McCool, Thomas
  - McCord, David
  - McCormick, Charles Graham, Rev.
  - McCormick, Thomas J., [2 folders]
  - McConnell, Emma
  - McDonald, Janet
  - McFarland, Jean H.
  - McGee, C. Douglas
  - McGee, Mary
  - McGhee, George C.
  - McGilvray, Donald C.
  - McGlinchey, Thomas J.
  - McGrew, Julia
  - McHugh, Thomas
  - McIntosh, Robert P.
  - McKean, Ida P.
  - McKenzie, Margaret
  - McKenzie, Nancy F.
  - McKinney, Audrey M.
  - McKinney, Thomas F.
  - McKitrick, Eric L.
  - McLaughlin, Elsie B.
  - McLaughlin, Jean I.
  - McLaughlin, Mary Martin
  - McNamara, Mary Jo
  - McVey, Frances Jewell (trustee)
  - Mead, Margaret
  - Meade, Andrew
  - Meade, Elizabeth
  - Meadows, Carol Jean
  - Mehaffey, Leathem
  - Mellon, Mary Conover (VC 1926)
  - Mellott, Beatrice Annette
  - Meltzer, Jamie
  - Menand, Louis
  - Mendelowitz, Paul
  - Mendez, Ignacio
  - Menzel, Johanna M. - SEE Meskill, Johanna
  - Mercadante, Thomas J. C.
  - Mercer, Caroline G.
  - Merrell, James H.
  - Merrick, Chester W. (Gate Watchman)
  - Merriell, David M., [2 folders]
  - Merrill, William P. (trustee)
  - Meskill, Johanna (Menzel)
  - Metzger, L. Paul
  - Meyer, Catherine
  - Michaels, Joan P. (Mrs. Anthony T.)
  - Mickel, Maxine A.
  - Middleton, Robert, [3 folders]
  - Milinowski, Marta, [2 folders]
  - Miller, Irvin
  - Miller, John P.
  - Miller, John Richardson
  - Miller, Maria Tastevin
  - Miller, Michael R.
  - Miller, William A.
  - Millones, Peter (trustee)
  - Mills, Herbert Elmer
  - Mills, Sally Diann
  - Miner, Janet Kiehle
  - Minturn, Karen
  - Miringoff, Helen
  - Misek, Linda D.
  - Mistral, Gabriela
  - Mitchell, Eleanor
  - Mitchell, Joyce
  - Mitchell, Marion Louise
  - Mitchell, Rebecca M.
  - Mitchell, William
  - Moffat, S. Bruce
  - Moldenke, Alison F.
  - Molin, Alma Luckau, [2 folders]
  - Moll, Richard W., [2 folders]
  - Monnier, Mathilde
  - Montalto, Helen
  - Monteux, Claude, [5 folders]
  - Montgomery, David C.
  - Montoya, James
  - Mooney, Patricia M.
  - Moore, Deborah Dash
  - Moore, Emmeline
  - Moore, J. Leverett
  - Moore, Suzanne L.
  - Morales, Hilda
  - Moran, Sue Ellen
  - More, Bruce E., 1968-1969
  - Morgan, Bryant T.
  - Morgan, Henry G.
  - Morgan, Jane, 1962-1967
  - Morgan, Shepard A. (trustee)
  - Morgan, Susan
  - Morley, John
  - Morrin, Anette
  - Morrin, Peter
  - Morris, Ray (trustee)
  - Morris, Ruby (Turner) Norris (VC 1929)
  - Morriss, Annette
  - Morse, Meredith
  - Morse, Samuel F.B. (trustee), [3 folders]
  - Morton, Levi P. (trustee), 1892-1905
  - Moses, William Bryan, Jr. (trustee)
  - Mosher, Eliza M.
  - Moskalew, Walter
  - Moss, Howard
  - Moss, James A.
  - Mosscrop, Alfreda, [2 folders]
  - Mothersill, Mary
  - Moulton, Charles W. (and Mrs. Moulton)
  - Mucci, Joseph
  - Muller, Helen (Maguire) (trustee), 1944-1945
  - Mullin, Lenore Restifo
  - Muncie, Margaret, Rev.
  - Muncie, Rita
  - Murphy, Clyde E.
  - Murphy, Joan Elizabeth
  - Murra, John V.
  - Murray, Pauli
  - Mursin, Tatiana
  - Murtaugh, James F.
  - Musacchio, Jacqueline
  - Musgrave, Peggy B.
  - Musolf, Lloyd D.
  - Musolf, William I. (trustee)
  - Mustonen, Anne R.
  - Mutone, Paul
  - Myers, Margaret G.
  - Myers, William I (Trustee)
- N
  - Nad-Nko
  - Noo-Nys
  - Nason, John W. (trustee)
  - Nathan, Otto
  - Needleman, Martin L.
  - Neely, Florence E.
  - Neimeth, Pamela
  - Nelbach, Inez
  - Nelson, Marianne L.
  - Nelson, Theodor
  - Nettleton, George H.
  - Nevins, Mary Ann
  - Newcomer, Mabel, [5 folders]
  - Newman, Murray Lee
  - Newman, Richard A.
  - Newton, Abba A.
  - Newton, Virginia
  - Nichols, Faith
  - Nichols, Judy
  - Nichols, Marie-Christine
  - Nicholson, Charles B.
  - Nickford, Juan
  - Niebuhr, Richard R.
  - Nier, Henry J.
  - Nixon, Robert, [3 folders]
  - Nkondo, Gessler Moses
  - Nochlin, Linda Weinberg, [5 folders]
  - Nochlin, Philip
  - Noonan, Linda Ristine
  - Norindr, Panivong
  - Norman, Jeffrey
  - Norrod, E Pinina
  - North, Helen
  - Northrop, Paul A.
  - Norton, Theodore M.
  - Nourse, James
  - Nourse, Mary Pemberton
  - Novack, David E.
  - Novoa, Sofia
  - Nwabuoku, Emeke
  - Nyfenger, Thomas
- O
  - Oak-Ozm
  - Oakley, Violet
  - O'Brian, George
  - O’Connor, John M., 1964-1968
  - Odlozilik, Otakar
  - Ogden, Daniel M.
  - O’Grady, Marcella - SEE Boveri, Marcella O’Grady
  - Ohmann, Carol Burke, 1964-
  - O'Keefe, Deborah J.
  - Okin, Susan Moller
  - Oktay, Elizabeth J.
  - Olafson, Frederick A.
  - Oldcorn, Anthony
  - Ollila, Paul W.
  - Olmstead, Frederic Law
  - Olsen, Donald J.
  - Olson, Lawrence
  - Olson, Margaret Pitoniak, 1975
  - O'Malley, M.
  - O'Meara, John J.
  - Omwake, Eveline
  - O’Neill, George O. (trustee)
  - Oppenheimer, Martin
  - Oppens, Ursula
  - O'Reily, Catherine
  - Organski, Katherine Fox
  - Orton, James, [6 folders]
  - Osborne, C. William
  - Osgood, Philips E. (trustee)
  - O’Shea, Theresa A.
  - Ostroff, Anthony
  - Ostrovsky, Everett S.
  - Ostrow, Steven F.
  - Ozmucur, Suleyman
- P
  - Pack-Pay
  - Peab-Phil
  - Picc-Pitt
  - Plum-Powe
  - Preg-Pyle
  - Page, Arthur W. (trustee)
  - Page, Barbara
  - Palliser, Helen L.
  - Palmer, Jean C.
  - Palmer, Josephine S., 1968-1973
  - Palmer, Marlene K.
  - Palmer, Margaret S.
  - Palmer, Nancy
  - Palmer, Ralph
  - Palmieri, Patricia Ann
  - Pamplume, Louis
  - Panvini, Willa
  - Pape, Sabrina Weiss
  - Pappas, Peter C.
  - Paris-Steffens, Rodrigo
  - Park, William E. (trustee)
  - Parker, Lloyd R., Jr.
  - Parker, Raymon
  - Parks, Robert E.
  - Parmly, Duncan D. (trustee)
  - Parrish, Carl
  - Parrish, Catherine
  - Partridge, Denny
  - Paschal, Carolyn Smith, [2 folders]
  - Paterson, Mabel, 1954
  - Patterson, Cynthia Burchell
  - Patton, Julia
  - Paul-Emile, Barbara Taylor
  - Paul-Emile, Serge
  - Paulus, David L.
  - Pearl, Alexander M.
  - Pearson, Donald M. (wife: Kathleen Funk), [2 folders]
  - Pearson, Elizabeth Clawson (Mrs. Homer)
  - Pearson, Homer (wife: Elizabeth Clawson), [2 folders]
  - Pearson, Kathleen Funk (Mrs. Donald)
  - Pearson, Margaret
  - Peck, H. Daniel
  - Peck, John
  - Peebles, Rose Jeffries
  - Peirce, John W., [2 folders]
  - Pell, Herbert Claiborne
  - Pellegrini, Anthony Louis, 1956-
  - Pelton, H.V. (trustee)
  - Penney, James
  - Pennock, Clarice
  - Pennock, Clarice H. L.
  - Perera, Victor
  - Periolat-Czula, Jeanne
  - Perkins, Dorothy Elizabeth
  - Perlmutter, Betty
  - Perlstein, Daniel
  - Perrault, Madeleine A., 1966-1969
  - Perry, Jeannette (VC 1904), 1948-1952
  - Perry, Marva J.
  - Perry, Norma
  - Peters, G. Moore (trustee)
  - Peterson, Lloyd
  - Peterson, Margery Betty
  - Pettee, Julia E., 1899
  - Petty, John R (trustee)
  - Pflueger, Friedrich
  - Pfuetze, Louise G. (Mrs. Paul)
  - Pfuetze, Paul E., [7 folders]
  - Pfuetze, Walter (son of Paul?)
  - Pfund, Marion C.
  - Phagan, Patricia
  - Phakamile, David Livington
  - Phillips, Rachel
  - Phillips, Sandra S.
  - Piccirilli, Bruno
  - Piccirilli, Maria (de Negri)
  - Piccolomini, Manfredi
  - Pick, Peter
  - Pick, Robert F. (non VC)
  - Pickens, Lucien Alton
  - Pierce, Barbara
  - Pierce, Charles Eliot, Jr.
  - Pierce, George T. (trustee)
  - Pierce, Madelene E.
  - Pike-Tay, Anne
  - Pilcher, Lewis E.
  - Pillsbury, Mary Boyden
  - Pin, Emile Jean
  - Pine, Patricia, 1974-1975
  - Pippin, Anne Newton
  - Pirnie, Malcolm (trustee)
  - Pirouz, Kamrouz
  - Pitcher, Oliver
  - Plum, Dorothy A., [4 folders]
  - Plunkett, Mary Alys
  - Poggioli, Peter A.
  - Poinsignon, Corinne, 1957-1971
  - Pokorny, Elizabeth Hird
  - Polacko, Amy
  - Poletti, Mrs. Charles (trustee)
  - Polk, George W. (comptroller)
  - Pollock, Luella R.
  - Poltoratzky, Marianna A.
  - Pomeroy, Sara B.
  - Pommer, Linda Nochlin Weinberg (SEE Nochlin, Linda)
  - Pommer, Richard, [2 folders]
  - Pope, Liston (trustee)
  - Pope, Randolph D.
  - Popoli, Al
  - Porter, Alan
  - Porter, Jean M.
  - Porter, Kenneth Wiggins, [2 folders]
  - Porter, Quincy
  - Porter, Robert E., 1966-1967
  - Posner, Julia
  - Possiedi, Paolo, 1968-1971
  - Post, Charles Gordon, [3 folders]
  - Post, Thomas C.
  - Potash, Betty
  - Potholm, Christian P.
  - Potter, Henry C. (trustee)
  - Potter, Louise
  - Potter, Margaret
  - Potts, Abbie Findlay
  - Pounder, Robert
  - Powell, Elizabeth M.
  - Pratt, Charles Millard (trustee)
  - Pratt, Richardson (trustee)
  - Pratt, Richardson, Jr. (trustee)
  - Precht - SEE C. Kapp
  - Prelle, Myra Jean
  - Preston, Laura
  - Price, Barry
  - Price, Charlotte A. (Mrs. Peter), 1966-1969
  - Price, James Parker
  - Prins, Jack, 1969-1971
  - Pritchard, William H.
  - Pritchett, John Perry
  - Procik, Catherine E.
  - Proctor, Redfield (trustee)
  - Proffitt, L. Grace
  - Prothero, Donald
  - Puglisi, Roberta A.
  - Pulver, William
  - Pumplin, Paula Leigh
  - Punsoni, Arthur
  - Purcell, Elizabeth Runkle (trustee)
  - Purcell, Frank
  - Putkoski, Joan
  - Putnam, Helen Cordelia
  - Pyle, Beatrice A.
  - Pyle, Cynthia M.
- Q
  - Qua-Qui
  - Queen, J. Michael Jr.
  - Quinn, Betty Hedberg
  - Quinn, Seabury, 1960-
- R
  - Rac-Reit
  - Reed-Rey
  - Richf-Riv
  - Rhe-Richa
  - Roa-Roberts
  - Robertso-Roos
  - Rose-Rosm
  - Ross-Rossi
  - Rot-Roz
  - Rub-Rui
  - Run-Rya
  - Raeburn, Vicki
  - Ragusa, Olga
  - Raimondi, Matthew
  - Rainey, Peter M.
  - Ramey, O. Jean (Mrs.), 1970-1971
  - Ramsey, Carol J.
  - Rand, Helen
  - Randolph, Francis F. (trustee), [4 folders]
  - Randolph, Francis F, Jr. (trustee)
  - Randolph, Mary (Hill) (trustee)
  - Ransom, Harry Howe
  - Ransom, Sarah B.
  - Ranung, Karen
  - Ranzoni, Francis
  - Ranzoni, Jane
  - Rappaport, Rhoda
  - Rappleye, Dr. Willard C. (trustee)
  - Rashid, Ismail
  - Rauch, Roberta Brown, 1932-
  - Raw, Silvia S.
  - Raybold, Dorothy Spencer
  - Rayfield, Ben
  - Raymond, Cornelia M., [2 folders]
  - Raymond, John Howard, [4 folders]
  - Reau, A. Cecille
  - Rebelein, Robert
  - Rebhuhn, Deborah
  - Reed, Amy L.
  - Reed, Myra Jean
  - Reed, Susan
  - Regnier, Jerome P. M., [2 folders]
  - Regunberg, Bernice
  - Rehberg, Cindy
  - Rehwoldt, Robert E., 1962-1967
  - Reid, Joan Elizabeth
  - Reilly, Edward R.
  - Reilly, Marion
  - Reimer, Sarah Harrison
  - Rein, Joanne H.
  - Reiss, Julie
  - Reiss, Steven A. (“young trustee”)
  - Renwick, James, Jr. (architect of Main building)
  - Resmer, Mark A.
  - Reynolds, Helen Wilkinson
  - Reynolds, Myra
  - Reynolds, William H.
  - Rheinstein, Alfred (trustee)
  - Rice, J. Valentine
  - Rich, Nancy Carol
  - Richards, Edith Jean
  - Richards, Elizabeth M.
  - Richards, Ellen (Swallow), [11 folders]
  - Richards, Keene
  - Richardson, Allen
  - Richardson, Kathleen S.
  - Richardson, Sophia
  - Richey, F. Elizabeth, [2 folders]
  - Richrath, Agathe Wilhelmine
  - Richter, Melissa Lewis
  - Rickarby, Sarah
  - Riess, Julie